

Ehsan Norouzi

BackEnd Developer(Django)

Contact

- Ehsannorouzi@protonmail.com
- 09109558446
- MyWebsite
- LinkedIn
- GitHub
- 💡 Iran, Hamedan

Expertise

- Python
- Django
- DRF
- Vue.js
- Vuetify
- Git
- Linux
- Docker

Certifications

Django - LinkedIn 2022 Certificate Id: ATRSEF6aWpkzNJ0rtP9tG9MIaE9Y

Education

2021-Present Shamsipour Technical and Vocational College Electrical and Electronics Engineering Tehran ,Iran

About me

I have over three years of experience in software industry with dominated history of working with python and django.

I do programming with interest and I use every opportunity to gain my experience and growth. I am also familiar with working as a team and I can work well with the team.

Work Experience

100Negar 2021-2022

I worked on the Negar 100 project using Django, DRF, All Auth in BackEnd and Vue Cli, Vuetify, Axios in FrontEnd. The strength of this website is its powerful admin panel.

Back-end Developer 2021- 2022

I'm currently exploring and learning advanced topics of back-end development and developing different websites in Django framework